https://www.wcbi.com/contest-privacy-statement/

Store Coupons
Click & Save Coupons!
your password
Forgot your password?
your email
A password will be e-mailed to you.
LATEST NEWS
Baptist Memorial Hospital – Golden Triangle set to receive 500 doses of the COVID-19 vaccine
Coronavirus Information
Stephen Pimpo -
December 10, 2020 0
COLUMBUS, MISS. (WCBI) - As advisors to the Food and Drug Administration met to discuss approving Pfizer’s COVID-19 vaccine Thursday, hospitals in North Mississippi...
Read more
Vardaman Residents In Mourning After Child Struck And Killed By 18 Wheeler
Local News
Allie Martin -
December 10, 2020 0
VARDAMAN, MISS. (WCBI) - Residents in Vardaman and throughout Calhoun County are in mourning after a 7 year old was struck and killed by...
Read more
School districts discuss student safety plan after holiday season
Local News
Stephanie Poole -
December 10, 2020 0
COLUMBUS, Miss. (WCBI)- Two more school districts in our area release details on learning models offered to students after Christmas break.
More than 3,300 students...
Read more
Louisville High School will go to virtual learning until the 18th of December
Local News
Mary Carroll Sullivan -
December 10, 2020 0
LOUISVILLE, MISS. (WCBI) - Late today, families with students attending Louisville High School sent a note home letting them know the school will be...
Read more
Congress approved money to renovate the federal courthouse in Aberdeen
Local News
Joey Barnes -
December 10, 2020 0
ABERDEEN, MISS. (WCBI) - Congress approves money to renovate the federal courthouse in Aberdeen.
24.3 million dollars will be used to replace the HVAC system,...
Read more
MSU will return for the spring 2021 semester on January 11th
Local News
Joey Barnes -
December 10, 2020 0
STARKVILLE, MISS. (WCBI) - A growing number of COVID-19 cases and upcoming holiday celebrations is causing Mississippi State to delay the start of its...
Read more
Due to COVID-19 Amory Middle School will return to virtual learning
Local News
Joey Barnes -
December 10, 2020 0
AMORY, MISS. (WCBI) - Positive COVID-19 tests are behind a move to make Amory Middle School virtual.
The school district reports three positive cases in...
Read more
City of Macon has reinstated a curfew in response to COVID-19
Local News
Aundrea Self -
December 10, 2020 0
MACON, MISS. (WCBI) - The city of Macon has reinstated a curfew in response to the COVID-19 pandemic.
The board of alderman passed an ordinance...
Read more
Sports
SPORTS SECTIONSLocal Sports
College Sports
The EndZone
Student Athlete of the Month
Player of the Week
2020 High School Football Tour
SPORTS NEWS
Louisville Wildcats Win 2020 4A State Title
High School Sports
Courtney Robb -
December 5, 2020 0
The Wildcats topped the Hornets, 15-14 to win the team's 10th state championship in program history.
Read more
Calhoun City Falls to Taylorsville in 2A Title Game
High School Sports
Courtney Robb -
December 5, 2020 0
WATCH: Highlights from the MHSAA 2A state championship game between Calhoun City and Taylorsville.
Read more
West Point Comes Up Short in 5A Title Game Against West Jones
High School Sports
Courtney Robb -
December 5, 2020 0
WATCH: For the first time since 2015, 5A has a new state champion after West Jones knocked off West Point 33-27.
Read more
Player of the Week: Noxubee County’s Bobby Shanklin
High School Sports
Chris Bolton -
December 2, 2020 0
Noxubee County plays for the 3A state title at 11am Friday, December 4th at Jackson Veterans Memorial Stadium.
Read more
WATCH: EndZone Top 5 Plays from the finale
High School Sports
Jon Sokoloff -
November 30, 2020 0
WATCH: Top 5 Plays from EndZone's finale
Read more
Ole Miss Defeats Mississippi State in 2020 Egg Bowl
College Sports
Chris Bolton -
November 28, 2020 0
The Rebels will not be in action next week on December 5. Dates and times of matchups with LSU and Texas A&M will be announced at a later date.
Read more
2020 Egg Bowl Special
College Sports
Jon Sokoloff -
November 28, 2020 0
WATCH: The WCBI Sports Team previews the 2020 Egg Bowl matchup while also giving some important context on the rivalry.
Read more
2020 WCBI EndZone Finale
EndZone
Chris Bolton -
November 28, 2020 0
WATCH: 2020 WCBI EndZone Finale
Jon and Chris put a bow on the 2020 high school football season.
Read more
Weather
WEATHER SECTIONSLatest Forecast
Accuweather Forecast
Interactive Radar & Alerts
Severe Weather Center
Local River Forecast
ALFA Skycam Network
December 10, 2020 0
While we're not expecting a complete washout this weekend, you will have to dodge some showers if you plan to be out. Fortunately, no...
Read more
A warm and sunny Thursday before rain chances return
Local News
Vanessa Alonso -
December 10, 2020 0
SUMMARY: Who's ready for the 70s? For early December, we'll take this and the sunshine. Enjoy this while you can because rain chances will...
Read more
Sunny and warm Thursday, rain Saturday morning
Local News
Trevor Birchett -
December 9, 2020 0
Temperatures will continue to warm up over the next several days with highs near 70 on Thursday and Friday. Rain will move in Friday...
Read more
A warmer & beautiful next few days
Local News
Vanessa Alonso -
December 9, 2020 0
SUMMARY: The 60s are making a comeback over the next several days as warmer air filters back in to our area for the second...
Read more
Slightly warmer by Wednesday, rain on the way
Local News
Trevor Birchett -
December 8, 2020 0
Temperatures will slowly warm up over the next several days with highs back into the mid 60s for the second half of the week....
Read more
A warming trend is on the way
Local News
Vanessa Alonso -
December 8, 2020 0
SUMMARY: A very nice next few days are expected for us here in north Mississippi and west Alabama with highs back into the 60s...
Read more
Sunshine continues for the next several days
Local News
Trevor Birchett -
December 7, 2020 0
We'll enjoy a nice stretch of weather for the next several days with highs back into the 60s for the middle of the week....
Read more
Quiet and cool as we begin the new workweek
Local News
Vanessa Alonso -
December 7, 2020 0
SUMMARY: It's going to be a pretty quiet workweek overall with our weather. High temperatures will be on the cool side in the 50s,...
Read more
Features
WCBI Special Features
WCBI’s After Hours
Back in 2
Behind the Screen
Holiday Shopping with WCBI
Mom to Mom
Store Coupons
Click & Save Coupons!
Pets Page
Local Events
Station
Video Services of WCBI
About WCBI-TV
CW TV Shows
What’s On
Meet the WCBI Team
LATEST NEWS
Baptist Memorial Hospital – Golden Triangle set to receive 500 doses of the COVID-19 vaccine
Coronavirus Information
Stephen Pimpo -
December 10, 2020 0
COLUMBUS, MISS. (WCBI) - As advisors to the Food and Drug Administration met to discuss approving Pfizer’s COVID-19 vaccine Thursday, hospitals in North Mississippi...
Read more
Vardaman Residents In Mourning After Child Struck And Killed By 18 Wheeler
Local News
Allie Martin -
December 10, 2020 0
VARDAMAN, MISS. (WCBI) - Residents in Vardaman and throughout Calhoun County are in mourning after a 7 year old was struck and killed by...
Read more
School districts discuss student safety plan after holiday season
Local News
Stephanie Poole -
December 10, 2020 0
COLUMBUS, Miss. (WCBI)- Two more school districts in our area release details on learning models offered to students after Christmas break.
More than 3,300 students...
Read more
Louisville High School will go to virtual learning until the 18th of December
Local News
Mary Carroll Sullivan -
December 10, 2020 0
LOUISVILLE, MISS. (WCBI) - Late today, families with students attending Louisville High School sent a note home letting them know the school will be...
Read more
Congress approved money to renovate the federal courthouse in Aberdeen
Local News
Joey Barnes -
December 10, 2020 0
ABERDEEN, MISS. (WCBI) - Congress approves money to renovate the federal courthouse in Aberdeen.
24.3 million dollars will be used to replace the HVAC system,...
Read more
MSU will return for the spring 2021 semester on January 11th
Local News
Joey Barnes -
December 10, 2020 0
STARKVILLE, MISS. (WCBI) - A growing number of COVID-19 cases and upcoming holiday celebrations is causing Mississippi State to delay the start of its...
Read more
Due to COVID-19 Amory Middle School will return to virtual learning
Local News
Joey Barnes -
December 10, 2020 0
AMORY, MISS. (WCBI) - Positive COVID-19 tests are behind a move to make Amory Middle School virtual.
The school district reports three positive cases in...
Read more
City of Macon has reinstated a curfew in response to COVID-19
Local News
Aundrea Self -
December 10, 2020 0
MACON, MISS. (WCBI) - The city of Macon has reinstated a curfew in response to the COVID-19 pandemic.
The board of alderman passed an ordinance...
Read more
Sports
SPORTS SECTIONSLocal Sports
College Sports
The EndZone
Student Athlete of the Month
Player of the Week
2020 High School Football Tour
SPORTS NEWS
Louisville Wildcats Win 2020 4A State Title
High School Sports
Courtney Robb -
December 5, 2020 0
The Wildcats topped the Hornets, 15-14 to win the team's 10th state championship in program history.
Read more
Calhoun City Falls to Taylorsville in 2A Title Game
High School Sports
Courtney Robb -
December 5, 2020 0
WATCH: Highlights from the MHSAA 2A state championship game between Calhoun City and Taylorsville.
Read more
West Point Comes Up Short in 5A Title Game Against West Jones
High School Sports
Courtney Robb -
December 5, 2020 0
WATCH: For the first time since 2015, 5A has a new state champion after West Jones knocked off West Point 33-27.
Read more
Player of the Week: Noxubee County’s Bobby Shanklin
High School Sports
Chris Bolton -
December 2, 2020 0
Noxubee County plays for the 3A state title at 11am Friday, December 4th at Jackson Veterans Memorial Stadium.
Read more
WATCH: EndZone Top 5 Plays from the finale
High School Sports
Jon Sokoloff -
November 30, 2020 0
WATCH: Top 5 Plays from EndZone's finale
Read more
Ole Miss Defeats Mississippi State in 2020 Egg Bowl
College Sports
Chris Bolton -
November 28, 2020 0
The Rebels will not be in action next week on December 5. Dates and times of matchups with LSU and Texas A&M will be announced at a later date.
Read more
2020 Egg Bowl Special
College Sports
Jon Sokoloff -
November 28, 2020 0
WATCH: The WCBI Sports Team previews the 2020 Egg Bowl matchup while also giving some important context on the rivalry.
Read more
2020 WCBI EndZone Finale
EndZone
Chris Bolton -
November 28, 2020 0
WATCH: 2020 WCBI EndZone Finale
Jon and Chris put a bow on the 2020 high school football season.
Read more
Weather
WEATHER SECTIONSLatest Forecast
Accuweather Forecast
Interactive Radar & Alerts
Severe Weather Center
Local River Forecast
ALFA Skycam Network
December 10, 2020 0
While we're not expecting a complete washout this weekend, you will have to dodge some showers if you plan to be out. Fortunately, no...
Read more
A warm and sunny Thursday before rain chances return
Local News
Vanessa Alonso -
December 10, 2020 0
SUMMARY: Who's ready for the 70s? For early December, we'll take this and the sunshine. Enjoy this while you can because rain chances will...
Read more
Sunny and warm Thursday, rain Saturday morning
Local News
Trevor Birchett -
December 9, 2020 0
Temperatures will continue to warm up over the next several days with highs near 70 on Thursday and Friday. Rain will move in Friday...
Read more
A warmer & beautiful next few days
Local News
Vanessa Alonso -
December 9, 2020 0
SUMMARY: The 60s are making a comeback over the next several days as warmer air filters back in to our area for the second...
Read more
Slightly warmer by Wednesday, rain on the way
Local News
Trevor Birchett -
December 8, 2020 0
Temperatures will slowly warm up over the next several days with highs back into the mid 60s for the second half of the week....
Read more
A warming trend is on the way
Local News
Vanessa Alonso -
December 8, 2020 0
SUMMARY: A very nice next few days are expected for us here in north Mississippi and west Alabama with highs back into the 60s...
Read more
Sunshine continues for the next several days
Local News
Trevor Birchett -
December 7, 2020 0
We'll enjoy a nice stretch of weather for the next several days with highs back into the 60s for the middle of the week....
Read more
Quiet and cool as we begin the new workweek
Local News
Vanessa Alonso -
December 7, 2020 0
SUMMARY: It's going to be a pretty quiet workweek overall with our weather. High temperatures will be on the cool side in the 50s,...
Read more
Features
WCBI Special Features
WCBI’s After Hours
Back in 2
Behind the Screen
Holiday Shopping with WCBI
Mom to Mom
Store Coupons
Click & Save Coupons!
Pets Page
Local Events
Station
Video Services of WCBI
About WCBI-TV
CW TV Shows
What’s On
Meet the WCBI Team
Our Commitment to Privacy
WCBI-TV respects the privacy of users on the Internet and has developed this privacy policy to protect user privacy on its Web sites. The purpose of this policy is to explain the types of information WCBI-TV obtains about the users of the Fall Poll site, how the information is obtained, how it is used, how it may be disclosed to others, and how users can restrict its use or disclosure.
Upickem Licensees
This site is operated in part by one or more licensees of Upickem, who in turn, license and maintain the Upickem service offered on this site. Upickem is responsible for all collection of information. If End User signs up for the Upickem Service through a licensee of Upickem, Upickem and such licensee shall co-own any End User Registration Information and content provided by End User. This Privacy Policy shall apply to both Upickem and such licensee.
Personally Identifiable Information
Online privacy concerns focus on the protection of “personally identifiable” information which an individual or customer reasonable expects to be kept private. As the term suggests, “personally identifiable” information is information that can be associated with a specific individual or entity.
The only personally identifiable information WCBI-TV obtains about individual users through our web sites is information supplied voluntarily by the user. Users interacting with our sites may provide WCBI-TV with name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, domain name or URL or other personally identifiable information that WCBI-TV may use for its own business purposes. WCBI-TV will collect and use this information for the ability to provide and change service, to anticipate and resolve problems with your service, for billing purposes, or to create or inform you of products and services that better meet your needs.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information
WCBI-TV does collect some non-personally identifiable generic information about our users as a means of measuring the effectiveness of our web sites. WCBI-TV identifies certain user information in the normal course of operation, but such information does not reveal a user’s personal identity. We collect this information only in the aggregate and use it to evaluate and improve our web sites. The following are examples of non-personally identifiable generic information:
IP Addresses: An IP address is a number that is assigned to a user’s computer whenever that user is using the World Wide Web. Web site servers must be able to identify individual computers by their IP address. WCBI-TV collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration security and to report aggregate usage information. WCBI-TV does not link IP addresses to any personally identifiable information.
Computer settings: Settings, technical and other information from your computer, such as your operating system, browser version, connectivity, various communication parameters and other information related to the operation and interaction of WCBI-TV web sites may be collected by WCBI-TV. Except as otherwise provided in this policy, WCBI-TV will use such information solely in order to provide technically appropriate formatting of information provided by WCBI-TV. The collection of this information will not include any personally identifiable information about you or any individual user.
Cookies
Cookies are pieces of information that are used for record keeping purposes. Cookies allow WCBI-TV to save certain information about a user, such as individual preferences, in order to facilitate and enhance the user’s future activity on the WCBI-TV web site. WCBI-TV will not use cookies to retrieve information from a user’s computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. Except as otherwise provided in this policy, WCBI-TV shall not use information transferred through cookies for any promotional or marketing purposes, and shall not share that information with any third parties for any reason. A user may refuse cookies by turning off that feature on their web browser.
Disclosure
WCBI-TV will not sell, trade, or disclose to third parties any personally identifiable information derived from registration for or use of a WCBI-TV service without the consent of the customer, except as required by subpoena, search warrant, or court order pursuant to applicable law, regulation or legal process or in the case of imminent physical harm to the customer or others.
Non-Participation
Any user who does not wish to receive further contacts from WCBI-TV may write to PO Box 271, Columbus, MS 39701.
Data Security
WCBI-TV will protect the confidentiality of its customer’s personally identifiable information to the fullest extent possible and consistent with law and legitimate interests of WCBI-TV and its employees. To protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of such information, WCBI-TV has appropriate physical, electronic and management procedures in place.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact us by writing to PO Box 271, Columbus, MS 39701.
WCBI-TV is not responsible for the content or the privacy practices of non-WCBI-TV web sites, including web sites reached through a link on a WCBI-TV web site. Other web sites may have different privacy policies, or no policy. Users should review the privacy policies of any web site before providing personal information.
Should WCBI-TV modify its practices regarding the collection and use of information obtained from users in the future, this privacy policy will be amended to reflect such modifications.
CONTEST RULES
WHAT’S ON
Complete TV ProgrammingLOCAL EVENTS
We're everywhere you need us to be. #YourNewsLeader
Talk To UsTalk to WCBI’s anchors, reporters and meteorologists. When you see news happening, share it! We’d love to hear from you.
(662) 328-1224 | news@wcbi.com
201 5th Street South, Columbus, MS 39701
Watch UsWe live, work, and play right here in North Mississippi and West Alabama. We are your neighbors. We celebrate community and we tell your stories. We are the most trusted source for local news.
Closed Captioning
FCC REPORTS
EEO Public Reports
Get AlertsDownload the WCBI News App on your smart phone or tablet device to receive breaking news and weather push notifications the minute it happens.
Mobile App
HOMEAbout Us
Contact Us
Advertise
Meet The Team
Mobile App
Employment
NEWSLocal News
WCBI’s First Responder Shout Out!
